<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics on Economics, Politics, and Resources</title>
    <link>/categories/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics on Economics, Politics, and Resources</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>All the Republican Bullshit from the Last Year</title>
      <link>/2018/03/27/both-sides/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/27/both-sides/</guid>
      <description>In my last rant, I wrote that the narrative &amp;ldquo;both sides do it&amp;rdquo; is itself toxic. We need to diagnose the problem correctly before we can hope to solve it.
And the problem is the fucking Republicans.
Without further ado, this post hopes to catalogue the ways in which the GOP and right wing politics have corroded our political system.
 Climate change - For about 30 years, Republicans have consistently denied science, impugned the credibility of scientists, actively promoted coal and oil, prevented the COP21 agreement from being stringent, saddled future generations with worse climate, ignored the pleas of the rest of the world, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screw the GOP -  Baby&#39;s First Step into Politics</title>
      <link>/2018/02/25/screw-the-gop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/25/screw-the-gop/</guid>
      <description>To start all this off, I won&amp;rsquo;t be saying much of anything new, and it won&amp;rsquo;t be a very long piece. That said, these are things that must be said over and over, and perhaps someone new will see. That would be enough for me.
My point is: Donald Trump is clearly guilty. Of obstruction of justice, of &amp;ldquo;collusion,&amp;rdquo; of grift, of nepotism, and of many more sad, disappointing, and enraging acts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>