<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Economics, Politics, and Resources</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Economics, Politics, and Resources</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Some sweet new R packages</title>
      <link>/2018/02/22/some-sweet-new-r-packages/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/22/some-sweet-new-r-packages/</guid>
      <description>Packages infer
infer is a tidyverse-consistent package for statistical inference. However, infer is more exciting because it makes running a t-test more like how we learned it in stats class. That is, infer requires you to specify your explanatory and response variables, state your hypothesis with hypothesize, generate the permutations or simulations, then calculate your chosen statistic. It’s another step in the right direction for consistency and clarity, which is great for getting more people coding (and doing statistics properly).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflections on RStudio::conf2018</title>
      <link>/2018/02/06/reflections-on-rstudio-conf2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/06/reflections-on-rstudio-conf2018/</guid>
      <description>Photo Credit: Sharon Machlis
Heading North on I-5 in Rich&amp;rsquo;s baby blue Prius, we pass by brown hills and palm trees as San Diego fades in the rear view mirror. The smell of last night&amp;rsquo;s beach bonfire wafts from our jackets stowed in the back seat, and Google Maps notifies us we&amp;rsquo;re about 7 hours from our respective destinations: Berkeley and Davis, CA.
In San Diego for a two-day conference on all things R, RStudio::conf2018, our minds were jammed with new packages, novel workflows, project inspiration, and a grab-bag of ideas on storytelling, empathy, and collaboration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Niklas Lollo
PhD Student
Energy and Resources Group, UC Berkeley
NSF NRT Fellow, Data Science for the 21st Century
See my website for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>